cv.md 11/24/2021



Wijnand Karsens

Full Stack TypeScript Developer & Founder

Address: Kleine Beer 40, 9742 RJ, Groningen

Phone: (+31) 68190 4650

Email: wijnand@karsens.com

Website: www.karsens.com

Skills

Web Development

- JavaScript / TypeScript
- React
- Next.js
- HTML
- (S)CSS

App Development

- JavaScript / TypeScript
- React Native
- Expo.io

Full Stack MVP Development

- All of the above
- Node.js
- MySQL

Other

- Team Work
- Marketing
- Entrepreneurship

cv.md 11/24/2021

- Product Ownership
- Test Driven Development

Interests

- (Kite)surfing
- Tabletop games
- Travel
- Going out
- Writing
- Hiking

Profile

I am am motivated individual that prides himself in having a lot of experience in (full-stack) web- and appdevelopment, working extremely fast and creating high-quality end-products.

The coming years my plan is to use my coding and leadership skills to develop humane mobile- and webapps. I plan to get Senior Developer, Lead Developer, and CTO roles while growing my Software Development Agency.

Education

- 2017: Diploma University Of Groningen (RUG), Bachelor, Artificial Intelligence
- 2012: Diploma VWO, Zernike College Westerse Drift, Haren, The Netherlands

Experience



CoworkSurf

Timeframe September 2021 - present

Position Chief Technology Officer (CTO) & Co-Founder Stack React, Next.js, Node.js (Full Stack TypeScript)

Probably the project I'm most proud of. Together with the 3 other founders, within one month I have successfully launched the MVP website: a booking platform for shared housing for remote workers at surf locations. The hardest part of this app was the complex logic of booking accommodation, the Stripe integration, and the optimal image delivery. Have a look at www.coworksurf.com

CoworkSurf

cv.md 11/24/2021



Timeframe September 2021 - present

Position Chief Technology Officer (CTO) & Co-Founder Stack React, Next.js, Node.js (Full Stack TypeScript)

Probably the project I'm most proud of. Together with the 3 other founders, within one month I have successfully launched the MVP website: a booking platform for shared housing for remote workers at surf locations. The hardest part of this app was the complex logic of booking accommodation, the Stripe integration, and the optimal image delivery. Have a look at www.coworksurf.com



CoworkSurf

Timeframe September 2021 - present

Position Chief Technology Officer (CTO) & Co-Founder Stack React, Next.js, Node.js (Full Stack TypeScript)

Probably the project I'm most proud of. Together with the 3 other founders, within one month I have successfully launched the MVP website: a booking platform for shared housing for remote workers at surf locations. The hardest part of this app was the complex logic of booking accommodation, the Stripe integration, and the optimal image delivery. Have a look at www.coworksurf.com